Wait a minute, Farmanfarmian is speaking
and you're bogarting the symposium?
- Howard, I'm sorry, we would've...
- No, no, you're quark-blocking us.
(Leonard:)I don't know what to say.
(Leonard(opening door):)Wow.
- Howard...
- It's your Millennium Falcon...
(Howard:)...you and Chewbacca do
whatever you wanna do.
(Howard:)Me and Princess Leia here will find
some other way to spend the evening.
(Penny:)Howard, wait.
(Penny:)Sheldon, I think we should tell them.
(Sheldon:)Okay, sure.
(Sheldon:)I don't see a problem with that.
(Penny:)There's no symposium.
(Penny:)Leonard lied to me.
Isn't that right, Leonard?
(Penny:)Well...
(Leonard:)- I don't know what to say.
- It's okay, I do.
(Penny:)Look, Leonard is helping Sheldon
through a family crisis.
(Penny:)He made up the whole story about
the symposium with Dr. Farmanfarmian...
- Good for you.
- Ha! Yeah.
(Penny:)He didn't want Sheldon to be embarrassed.
There's nothing to be embarrassed about.